makhsoom.com 2019-06-24

# Base - Page - Makhsoom

### Privacy Policy

The makhsoom Website is operated by SCAS sal, "makhsoom" or "we" or "our" or "us"). Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information collected from you ("User" or "you" or "your"), what we do with it, with whom we share it, and how you can correct or change such information. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy carefully, especially before providing any personal data through the Service or the makhsoom Website. The makhsoom Website is operated in and controlled from the United States of America. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the makhsoom Website, or if you wish to unsubscribe from the Service (or any other services) on the makhsoom Website for which you have previously registered, please click here to go to our Contact Us form. You can unsubscribe from our newsletter by clicking on the unsubscribe button at the bottom of every email. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, all terms shall have the meaning defined in the Makhsoom End User Terms and Conditions.

### WE ENCOURAGE YOU TO READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING AND/OR USING THE SERVICE OR THE MAKHSOOM WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE Makhsoom END USER TERMS AND CONDITIONS. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, PLEASE EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE SERVICE OR THE MAKHSOOM WEBSITE.

### Protecting the Privacy of Minors

Minors under the age of 18 may not use the Service or the makhsoom Website. By accessing and/or using the Service or the makhsoom Website you are representing that you are at least 18 years of age and that you have the permission of your parent or guardian to use the Service and the makhsoom Website. We do not collect or maintain information from anyone known to be under the age of 18. If we obtain actual knowledge that a User is under the age of 18, we will take steps to remove that User's Personal Information from our records. makhsoom does not sell products for purchase by children, nor is any part of the makhsoom Website intentionally designed to attract the attention of anyone under the age of 18, however, we may offer Vouchers for children's products with the intention that they will be purchased by adults. If you are under 18, you must obtain the permission of a parent or guardian before submitting information in connection with the Service and the makhsoom Website.

### Types of Information We Collect

#### Personal Information

If you create an account and join Makhsoom in order to take advantage of the full range of services offered on the makhsoom Website, we ask for and record some Personal Information." "Personal Information" means information you knowingly choose to disclose to us, such as your name and email address, which information contains details about the identity of the User. We will use your email address to send you a daily email announcing the Voucher or Vouchers to be offered for that particular day. We may also use your email address to send you updates and news about the makhsoom Website. When you purchase a Voucher, you will need to submit your credit card number and other payment information so that our third-party service providers can process your payment for the Voucher. Such credit card information is also considered Personal Information.

#### Contributions

We store and may publicly display your contributions to the makhsoom Website in order to provide and enhance the services that we offer. When we display your contributions, we may do so together with your user name. "Contributions" refers to any content you submit or post to the makhsoom Website for public display, such as ratings, restaurant or spa reviews, comments, photos, facts, and other similar types of information. Please do not include information in your contributions that you expect to be kept private or that may infringe on the rights of any third parties.

#### Feedback

If you contact us to provide feedback, register a complaint, or ask a question, we will record any Personal Information and other content you provide in your communication so we can effectively respond to your communication.

#### Activity

We automatically record information relating to your use of the Service via the makhsoom Website (through the use of electronic tools such as cookies, web beacons or pixel tags), such as the searches you undertake, the pages you visit, your browser or phone type, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, requested Uniform Resource Locator ("URL"), referring URL, and timestamp information, and other similar types of information. We use this information to operate and administer the makhsoom Website and to provide the highest possible level of service to you.

#### Cookies and Other Navigational Tools

To enhance your experience with the makhsoom Website, we store cookies on your computer and we may use Web beacons or pixel tags. Pixel tags and web beacons are graphic images placed on certain pages on our makhsoom Website or in our emails to you that allow us to determine whether you have performed a specific action. Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies also allow us to collect non-personal information from you, like which pages you visited and what links you clicked on. Cookies, pixel tags and web beacons, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other Personal Information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering for the Service on the makhsoom Website. However, once you choose to furnish the makhsoom Website with Personal Information, this Personal Information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on the makhsoom Website. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at the makhsoom Website (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to the makhsoom Website), and to save your password in password-protected areas. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. In addition, we may use third party advertising companies to display advertisements on the makhsoom Website. As part of their service, they may place separate cookies on your computer. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by the makhsoom Website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third party. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the makhsoom Website may not work properly or at all.

### How We Use Your Information

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about the Service, and to offer you other products, programs, or services we believe may be of interest to you. We may also use your Personal Information to administer sweepstakes and contests.

We may use or disclose your information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

If we believe it is necessary, we may disclose your Personal Information to third parties in a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (i) take action regarding suspected illegal activities; (ii) investigate, enforce or apply our makhsoom End User Terms and Conditions or this Privacy Policy; (iii) comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order; or (iv) protect our rights, reputation, or property or that of our Users, affiliates, third parties, or the public. Please note that we are not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena, or other similar governmental request we may receive.

makhsoom may aggregate data and disclose such data only in aggregate and in a non-personally identifiable manner to third parties for marketing and promotional purposes (e.g., how many users responded to a particular Voucher or other offer, to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the makhsoom Website). Aggregated information does not identify any User individually.

We use information about which links have been followed and whether action has been taken on another party's website to improve our offerings and to customize the Service.

Technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, IP address, pages visited, and average time spent on our the makhsoom Website, may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve our website design and functionality.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the makhsoom Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to the makhsoom Website and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you choose to use the separate products or services offered by such third-party advertising companies, disclose information to the providers, and/or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their privacy policy. You should evaluate their practices before deciding to use their products or services. 

### Release of Your Information to Third Parties

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we generally do not sell, trade, rent or share Personal Information that we collect with third parties unless we have your consent to do so.

From time to time, we provide offers from particular Merchants who, as part of the offer, request information on makhsoom customers who purchased the Voucher. In those cases, we share some of your Personal Information as well as your non-personal activity information with makhsoom Merchants. Sharing this information will allow a makhsoom Merchant to market directly to you should they choose to do so. Please note that we will only provide a makhsoom Merchant your information with an opt-in notice to you, in which you will have a chance to choose that makhsoom not give the makhsoom Merchant your Personal Information. We specifically disclaim any responsibility or liability for the actions of such makhsoom Merchant. While we inform them that they are only permitted to communicate with you for the purposes of the specific promotion with makhsoom, we do not have any responsibility for the actions of the makhsoom Merchant, and the actions of the makhsoom Merchant are not in our control.

We may provide some of our services and products through third parties. These third-party service providers perform certain administrative and promotional functions on our behalf. We also use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the makhsoom Website. We may share your Personal Information with such service providers to fulfill orders, deliver packages, send postal or email, administer contests or sweepstakes, remove repetitive information on customer lists, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, provide search results and links, process credit card payments, operate the makhsoom Website, troubleshoot, and provide customer service. We may also publish this information for promotional purposes or as a representative audience for advertisers. Please note that this is not Personal Information, only general summaries of the activities of our Users. Such data is collected on our behalf, and is owned and used by us.

We may also collect personal information from individuals and companies with whom we have business relationships and may have to also share their information with service providers to accomplish our administrative tasks. We encourage makhsoom Merchants and third-party service providers and advertising companies to adopt and post their own privacy policies. However, the use of your Personal Information by such parties is governed by the privacy policies of such parties and is not subject to our control. 

We may transfer your information to a third party in connection with a sale or acquisition of makhsoom or substantially all of its assets (or a merger of makhsoom with another company). If this occurs, the successor company would acquire the information we maintain, including Personal Information. However, Personal Information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy. 

### Security of Your Personal Information

While this Privacy Policy expresses makhsoom's standards for maintenance of Personal Information, makhsoom is not in a position to guarantee the standards will always be met. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in unintentional disclosure of your Personal Information. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. But no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage, is 100 percent secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Updating and Correcting Your Personal Information

We believe that you should have the ability to access and edit the Personal Information you provide us. You may change any of your Personal Information by clicking here go to our Contact Us form. Please indicate your name, address and email address, and what information you would like to update when you contact us. 

We encourage you to promptly update your Personal Information if it changes. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed; however, because we keep track of past transactions, you cannot delete information associated with past transactions on the makhsoom Website. In addition, it may be impossible for us to completely delete all of your information, even if you terminate your account or unsubscribe from the Service, because we periodically backup information.

### Notice of Privacy Rights to California Residents.

California law allows users of this Website that reside in California to know the third parties with whom we shared their Personal Information for those third parties' own direct marketing purposes. The type of information and instances in which we share such information is detailed in this Privacy Policy. However, if you are a resident of California and you would like to know the names and addresses of the specific third parties with whom we shared your Personal Information for their own direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and the categories of the Personal Information we shared, you should click here to go our Contact Us form. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what Personal Information you do not want us to share with third parties. The request should be sent to the attention of our legal department, and labeled "California Customer Choice Notice." Alternatively, you may send us a written request for such information to the address set forth below. Please allow 30 days for a response.

### How to Reach Us

If you wish to contact us on matters related to this policy, or any other matter related to the Service (including customer service inquiries), you can reach us using the contact details set forth below:

Makhsoom - Beirut - Damascus Road  
Lebanon  
E-mail: info@makhsoom.com  
Click here to go to our Contact Us form.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. You may review updates to our Makhsoom End User Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy at any time via links on the makhsoom Website. You agree to accept electronic communications and/or postings of an annual or revised Privacy Policy on the makhsoom Website and that such electronic communications or postings constitute notice to you of the Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify this policy from time to time, so please review it regularly. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, and/or by means of a notice on our home page.

The revised Privacy Policy is effective immediately when posted on the makhsoom Website. It is your responsibility to review the makhsoom Website and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Service and/or the makhsoom Website after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy. 

### Sole Statement

The foregoing statements, terms and conditions contained in this Privacy Policy represent the sole statement of our privacy policy, and no summary or other version, or other policy, in any form, including, without limitation, machine-generated, is valid.
